{
    "id": "87022246be7b4ad2b05c785211814b7d",
    "title": "Idioms and phrasal verbs exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "fe1a7f8ee6c54c7c851c567d143b30fb",
            "title": "Idioms And Phrases Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I have a …………………… . to pick with him. The other day he called me a liar.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "nail",
                        "bone",
                        "tooth"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was almost blown ……………………. by the wind.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "over",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Suddenly the barrel of gun powder blew ……………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He will never listen to us. Why should we waste our ………………… ?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "heart",
                        "mind",
                        "words",
                        "breath"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are …………………  to defeat the enemy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "racing",
                        "longing",
                        "burning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was carried ……………………… by his enthusiasm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "away",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You hit the nail on the ..................................... when you said that politics is a dirty game.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "toe",
                        "trunk",
                        "head"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He never thought that I would hit him in a …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "jiffy",
                        "flash",
                        "breeze"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I held my ……………………… when I first saw a tiger in the wildness.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "voice",
                        "breath",
                        "eyes"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was left ………………… and dry when a pickpocket deprived me of all my money.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "high",
                        "low",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}